

- +48 608 467 526
- ✓ szumny.marek@gmail.com
- MarekSzumny.com
- github.com/lukmarcus

Manual testing

- Creating test scenarios
- Regression testing
- Bug reporting
- API testing
- Quality control

Automated testing

- Cypress
- CSS selectors / XPath
- Postman / Newman

Tech Skills

- Jira / Github / Mantis
- TestLink / TestRail
- HTML / CSS / Bootstrap
- Browser Dev Tools
- GIT CLI
- SOI
- Linux
- Inkscape / GIMP

Soft Skills

- Scrum
- Meticulousness
- Accountability
- Proactivity
- Self-organization
- Teamwork
- Copywriting

Languages

- English B2
- Polish Native

Marek Szumny

A highly effective, ambitious, motivated and widely experienced engineer who spends the last few years of his professional career dealing with e-commerce processes automation including online store launching, sales platforms parametrization and configuration, integrations with BaseLinker, invoice & sales management software changes, data migrations, updates and improvements management, etc.

Creative mind, great team player, organizer and manager with a high level of soft skills, experienced in work and building good relationships with private and business clients.

Due to the fact, I was always related and I'm still closely related to technology, IT and gaming (analog also) industries I decided to go back to my roots and jump in again into the ocean of exciting opportunities which the IT industry is.

I'm 100% sure I want to stay in this exciting industry for a long time, so I'm investing all my time and effort every day to develop my technical skills and keep this career path.

Work Experience (Testing Related)

Manual Tester & Automation Tester

Upwork (Freelancing) | February 2023 - present

- Testing responsive websites (mobile + desktop)
- Retesting newly introduced features and fixes on dedicated endpoints
- Bug reporting & prioritization
- Writing automated Cypress tests

"Fundamentals of Software Testing" Course Attendant

QATestLab Training Center | April 2023

- Layout, Cross-browser Compatibility, Functional & Mobile testing
- Bug reporting (Mantis Bug Tracker)
- · Creating checklists
- Writing test cases (TestLink, TestRail)

Game Tester

Techland | March 2010 - May 2010

- Participation in projects: Dead Island, Call of Juarez: The Cartel, Nail'd
- Testing games on multiple platforms (PlayStation 3, Xbox 360, PC)
- Testing of platform-specific features (PS3 trophies / Xbox achievements, invites and multiplayer game progress, etc.)
- Business logic testing
- Bug reporting and monitoring in Mantis Bug Tracker
- Regression tests

Game Tester / Reviser

Portal Games | March 2005 - October 2006

- Mechanics testing and revision of the role-playing game Neuroshima 1.5 (ISBN: 83-921612-6-2) with the expansions
- Testing the board game *Neuroshima Hex!* (first edition) with the expansions
- Proofreading the magazine Gwiezdny Pirat (The Star Pirate) (ISSN: 1644-7689)
- Websites administration and management

Projects (Testing Related)

Tester & Copywriter @ HiveProjects.io

Wise-Team / Engrave | July 2018 - present

- Cataloguing and researching new projects
- Creating and publishing a newsletter about HiveProjects changes
- Project testing and bug reporting

Game Tester / Translator / Copywriter

Virtual Publisher MARK6 | November 2007 - present

- Translation and typesetting of Print & Play board games and expansions, role-playing games and expansions, board game rulebooks
- Testing of the board games: Evil Mansion & Theme Park Tycoon
- Testing of the role-playing games mechanics: Afterbomb Madness (ISBN: 978-83-930571-0-8)
 & Trójca 1.5
- Cooperation with the online portal Poltergeist (ISSN: 1898-2107)

Other Work Experience

E-commerce Process Automation Engineer

New Deal / DR Trading | July 2019 - March 2023

- Shopping platforms management (Allegro, Erli, Empik, Arena, Morele)
- Researching platforms which allows to create online stores, configuration and commissioning
- Online store management (FIT-NET fit-net.com.pl)
- Sales process handling and maintaining the technical side (updates, improvements, etc.)
- Plus, the duties from the previous position

Major projects / undertakings

- June September 2020 | Migration of the sales system for several Allegro accounts to the Baselinker integrator, with added support for courier companies
- September 2020 | Migration of the accounting and warehousing system from the offline system FS-Faktura to the online system *Fakturownia* and integration of its processes with Baselinker
- September December 2020 | Configuration and launch of a shop on Shoper platform;
 system integration with the biggest marketplaces: Erli, Empik, Arena, Morele

Technology & Product Development Specialist

New Deal / DR Trading | January 2015 - June 2019

- · Goods admission to the warehouse
- Physical control of quality and conformity with the order
- Offers content creation (text, photos, enhancement of photos/graphics)
- Template customization (HTML/CSS & WYSIWYG)
- Sales process design and analysis creation
 - o Offers modification suggestions (price, offers content, etc.)
 - Managing customer satisfaction / ensuring positive product feedback
- · Inventory management
- · Complaints process handling
- Introducing and testing various pricing strategies

Computer Service Technician

INTER-ES | June 2012 - May 2014

- Repair and maintenance of computer equipment (desktops, laptops, printers and peripheral)
- Installation and configuration of software (operating systems, office and security software)
- Diagnostics and troubleshooting
- Technical support for other employees, including assistance with troubleshooting and answering questions

Shop Assistant

Meta - Sports shops | August 2008 - February 2012

• Customer service and cash register operating

Other Projects

Community Manager @ #Polish

Blockchain Steem / Blockchain Hive | July 2016 - August 2018

- Co-creating a community of Polish bloggers
- Co-author of white-hat-hack of blockchain-based blogging platform Steemit (more details)

Board Game Club Manager

Board Game Club "Orbita Gier" | November 2022 - present

- Organization of weekly meetings
- Presentation of the board games and explaining their rules
- Contact with publishers and participation in nationwide events

Education

Wrocław University of Science and Technology

Faculty of Microsystem Electronics and Photonics, Program: Applied Electronics

2004 - 2007

Hobby

Board games, video games, pop culture, blogging, running.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Dournal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).